{"data":[{"question":"Have you plotted your data _____ a graph?","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"\n\nPrepositions of Place: at, in, on\n- At for a point: at the corner, at the bus stop, at the door, at the top of the page, at the front desk...\n- In for an enclosed space: in the garden, in London, in a box, in my wallet, in a industry...\n- On for a surface: on the wall, on the floor, on a page...\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"2"},{"question":"What features should one look for _____ a laptop?","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Use at with particular positions or places\n- Use in with a position or place, when something or someone is inside a larger thing such as a room\n- Use on with a position or place, when one thing is attached to or touching another\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"2"},{"question":"That singer has been _____ several talk shows recently.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- On: taking part in an activity or travelling somewhere","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"2"},{"question":"I was _____ the phone when my friend interrupted me.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n- On: using a machine or piece of equipment\nOn the phone: I am using the phone","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"2"},{"question":"Ralph has invested heavily _____ mutual funds","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- In: doing or affecting a particular kind of job","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"2"},{"question":"Heat two tablespoons of olive oil ____ a skillet over medium heat.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- Use at with particular positions or places\n- Use in with a position or place, when something or someone is inside a larger thing such as a room\n- Use on with a position or place, when one thing is attached to or touching another\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"2"},{"question":"He lived _____ a diet of rice and beans for several months.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"3","explain":"\n\n-  Live on something:  to eat a lot of a particular type of food","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"2"},{"question":"She was out of breath when she arrived _____ the office.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- In: into a container, place\n She's inside the office","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"2"},{"question":"The controller for Acme Corp. testified _____ the Senate hearing today.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"2","explain":"\n\n- Use at with particular positions or places\n- Use in with a position or place, when something or someone is inside a larger thing such as a room\n- Use on with a position or place, when one thing is attached to or touching another\n\n","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"2"},{"question":"_____ a recent study, researchers found a link between playing violent video games and violent behavior.","a":"in","b":"at","c":"on","answer":"1","explain":"\n\n- In: doing or affecting a particular kind of job","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"37","subcategorylv2":"4","type":"2"}]}